# **HAYREDDIN TUZEL**



#### **Personal**

♠ Address

Izmir

- **Phone number** 05317908874
- Email hayreddintuzel@gmail.com
- Website https://hayreddintuzel.com
- C∋ LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/hayreddintuzel/

#### **Interests**

- Trekking
- Watching series

I have been working in different areas of computer science since 2010. I was very familiar with defense technology because I had my license at Naval Academy. In this process, I completed my undergraduate with first degree. I conducted my studies academically at first. But I decided in 2016 that I could not continue my academic career after the political events in my country. Since 2017 I have developed myself on web programming. In this process, I have been involved in the construction of many websites and web apps.

I always open to challenges to improve myself. Now, I am working on Salesforce Commerce Cloud for more than 1.5 years.

# Work experience

#### **Full Stack Web Developer**

May 2016 - Sep 2018

Freelance

I worked as freelance developer and I created web apps with following technlogies:

- ReactJS
- VueJS
- NodeJS
- PHP / Laravel
- Wordpress
- Asterisk
- Amazon AWS
- GoLang
- Docker

I created many websites while was working as freelancer. In this process, I carried out all my relations with the customer myself. I found solutions for the customer's needs. I worked with many different designers and took part in finalizing the whole project from coding to deployment.

My main projects are;

- turacoon.com (Cambly-like platform for Turkish language education)
- besteditproof.com (Project management system for academic proofreading and editing)
- ekotify.com (Project management system for voice over projects)
- birebirci.com (Online education site)
- createtolearn.online (Textbook supporter site)
- setyourmotivation.com (Academic scale for media literacy)

In this process, I had the opportunity to develop myself to work on my own, my work discipline, process management, web technology basics, simple devops processes, and many software languages and technologies. Also, I was able to develop solutions against very demanding technologies and customer requests.

### SFCC Backend Developer

Sep 2018 - Present

**OSF** Digital

As long as I worked at OSF, I worked as a backend developer. However, due to my previous freelance experience, I occasionally solved front-end tasks, too.

I worked with a large project team of approximately 30 members, including FD and BD developers, QAs, and PMs at OSF. In the project where we adopt the Agile technique, we developed multiple features at the same time and fixed bugs.

I developed many features as the main developer. Also, I was able to develop some features myself alone. Although I was working in the role of developer, I developed solutions such as tech lead in some subprojects.

Some of the features I worked in this process were as follows;

- Subscription (SFCC and Zuora integration)
- Wishlist
- Loyalty Points and a lot of customization on SFCC's default promotion / campaign system
- Refund
- Worldpay 3DS version 2 (3DS Flex)
- Notification System for Customers
- Ownership (Another big integration with 3th party)
- Creating of some jobs for importing and exporting products, customers etc.
- And bug fix in almost all areas of SFCC

By working on these features, I gained experience on these submodules of SFCC:

- Pipelines
- Controllers
- Checkout Flow
- Promotion/Campaigns and Coupons
- Jobs
- Service Integrations
- SFRA
- Orders
- Products
- FD Javascript

My general responsibilities at OSF digital are:

- Code implementation,
- · Creation of pull requests,
- · Reviewing of Pull Requests,
- Analysis of customer requests and finding solutions,
- Giving estimation for customer's requests,
- · Creating a technical document,
- · Creating guides for our customers' business team,
- Bug fixing,
- Joining meetings with our teams,
- Joining meetings with our customers,
- Reporting to my Project Manager,
- Verification of the code I have implemented in CI environments,

#### **Education and Qualifications**

## **Computer Science**

Sep 2010 - Jul 2013

Naval Academy

I completed my undergraduate with first degree and 3.50 credit.

#### Skills

Salesforce Commerce
Cloud

Javascript (Reactjs, Vuejs,
Nodejs)

PHP (Laravel)

DevOps (Docker, Amazon
AWS)